eurotax.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Autovista Group

## Privacy at the Autovista Group

The information in this privacy notice relates to the privacy practices of Autovista Group Limited  of 5th Floor, Wellington House, 125 Strand, London WC2R 0AP, United Kingdom, and its [subsidiaries](https://www.autovistagroup.com/our-locations) (‘ **Autovista Group** ’, ‘ **we** ’, ‘ **us** ’).

We respect your right to privacy and are committed to complying with all applicable data protection legislation and to ensuring your privacy is protected. We take our related legal obligations seriously, have suitable measures in place to safeguard and secure the Personal Data you provide to us, and aim to be transparent at all times about our treatment of your personal data (‘ **Personal Data** ’ as defined in Art.4 (1) of the General Data Protection Regulation, ‘ **GDPR** ’).

This privacy notice explains your rights in relation to the Personal Data we hold about you and how:

  1. We use and protect that Personal Data;
  2. You can instruct us to limit the use of Personal Data about you;
  3. We safeguard your privacy and;
  4. We may disclose Personal Data about you to others.

### 1\. The scope of this privacy notice

This privacy notice governs our processing of your [Personal Data](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/what-personal-data_en)produce their own websites, events and digital content. When you use any service which is operated by a third party, the use of your Personal Data will be subject to their terms and conditions detailed in their privacy notice and not ours. If you have any concerns, please contact us at: dataprotection@autovistagroup.com.

### 2\. Collection and use of Personal Data

When you browse our website the only Personal Data we collect is your IP address. Apart from this information, your browsing is anonymous as no Personal Data is collected unless you register to use our products or to receive information from us such as newsletters, in which case we ask for your name, email address, telephone number and job title. We also collect some basic, anonymous technical information such as click sequences. This information is used to analyze your usage of the website and may be used to send targeted marketing campaigns. Your consent will be sought before any marketing content is sent. We aggregate non-personal information relating to the use of this website for statistical purposes but none of your Personal Data is made available to third parties.

### 3\. Registration and use of your Personal Data

When you register on the site using our sign-up processes in order that we may send you selected information, your Personal Data (name, email address, telephone number) is collected and stored. Unless you have given your consent, the data will not be disclosed to any third party except to the extent either allowed or required by law or where we have identified abusive or [non-compliant](https://www.autovistagroup.com/terms-conditions) use of the website. If you give us your approval to use your Personal Data, this data will be handled with the utmost respect for your privacy. Apart from the cases mentioned above, we only process the Personal Data provided by the individual and do not obtain Personal Data from publically accessible sources.

### 4\. Legal basis for processing Personal Data via our website

The legal basis for processing the Personal Data gathered from using the website is your consent given in the form of a tick box within the Eloqua Preference Centre on our website (see point 6) . You may withdraw consent at any time either by using the unsubscribe button, by by emailing us at [dataprotection@autovistagroup.com](mailto:dataprotection@autovistagroup.com) or by writing to us at the address at the bottom of this privacy notice.

### 5\. Cookies

If our website is to work properly, you will need to ensure that your web browser is set to accept cookies. A cookie is a small file (or record in a file) which the website can send to your browser which may then store it on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow us to analyse web traffic and to determine more popular areas of our website. Cookies also allow us to make our website more user friendly by allowing us to save all registration details or passwords so that you do not have to re-enter them every time you visit the website.  The cookie will stay on your computer and will only be used should you enter our website. Notwithstanding the above, you do not have to accept cookies and you should read the information that came with your web browser software to see how you can set up your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and to give you the opportunity to decide to accept or reject it. Our cookies will not transmit any information to us about you other than concerning your use of our website.

### 6\. Eloqua tracking technology used by our marketing emails

To personalise how we communicate with you, we use Eloqua Preference Centre for various pages on our websites and for the information we send to you. On the relevant pages, Eloqua will employ the use of cookies and JavaScript code for measuring usage and to access certain information. Eloqua will place a cookie on your device during your first visit to our website. We may use the Eloqua cookie and information from the JavaScript code to allow us to analyse your use of our website and our communications, so we can understand your interests and determine how to improve the communications we send to you.

Although this cookie does not contain any Personal Data about you, if you choose to register to receive individualised information communications, then we will link your Personal Data to the browsing information associated with the Eloqua cookie on your device to personalise the user experience for you.The cookie will become inactive after 2 years unless you delete it via your browser settings before then.

To opt-out of web monitoring specific to this website, please email your request to [insights@autovistagroup.com](mailto:insights@autovistagroup.com)

### 7\. Updates

As a recipient of the Autovista Group Daily Brief, you may from time to time, receive further communications and news about other services which may be available from us or our subsidiaries. If you would prefer not to receive such communications or updates, please send an email message to us at insights@autovistagroup.com with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line or click on the unsubscribe button at the bottom of the communication sent to you. Please also provide details of those email addresses to which further communications should not be sent.

### 8\. Updating your details

If any of the Personal Data that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address, or if you wish to delete your details, please tell us by sending an email to [insights@autovistagroup.com](mailto:insights@autovistagroup.com).

### 9\. Processing undertaken by us

In the UK, the trading subsidiary of the Autovista Group is Glass’s Information Services Limited, the publisher of Glass’s Guide. Glass’s Information Services Limited processes Personal Data in the UK and other Autovista Group subsidiaries process Personal Data in other EU countries. The following is a broad description of the way in which we as Data Controller process Personal Data. To understand in greater detail how your Personal Data is processed you may need to refer to any personal communications you have received in addition to this privacy notice or contact us on [dataprotection@autovistagroup.com](mailto:dataprotection@autovistagroup.com).

### 10\. Reasons / purposes for processing Personal Data

We process Personal Data to enable us to promote our goods and services and to maintain our accounts and records.

### 11\. Types / classes of Personal Data processed

We process Personal Data relevant to the reasons / purposes stated in 10 above. This may include:

  * Personal details
  * Financial details
  * Details regarding the goods or services provided

### **12\. Who the Personal Data may be shared with**

Where necessary or required, always in compliance with applicable Data Protection legislation, we may share the Personal Data we process with:

  * Central Government
  * Credit reference agencies
  * Suppliers and service providers
  * Debt collectors and tracing agencies
  * Financial organisations
  * Law enforcement or other investigatory agencies
  * Auditors

### **13\. Transfers**

Where necessary, Personal Data may be transferred to countries or territories around the world, in full compliance with applicable Data Protection legislation. This will only take place in cases where: 

  * the European Commission has decided that a third country ensures an adequate level of protection; 
  * the third party receiving the Personal Data has provided us with adequate safeguards in the form of standard data protection clauses approved by regulatory authorities; 
  * we comply with a code of conduct approved by a supervisory authority; 
  * we hold certification under an approved mechanism as provided for in applicable Data Protection legislation; or 
  * we have agreed contractual clauses authorised by a competent supervisory authority.

### **14\. Your rights**

The GDPR gives individuals greater control over how organisations process Personal Data and provides a number of [rights to the individual](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/rights-citizens_en) in relation to the use of their Personal Data, including:

  * The right to be informed
  * The right of access
  * The right to rectification
  * The right to erasure
  * The right to restrict processing
  * The right to data portability
  * The right to object to processing
  * Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling

If you have any questions relating to your rights under the GDPR please contact [us](mailto:dataprotection@autovistagroup.com) on dataprotection@autovistagroup.com.

### **15\. Retention of Personal Data**

Unless required by legislation or regulation we will not keep Personal Data relating to our customers for longer than three years after the last communication with the individual or the end of a contract with the individual’s employer.

### **16\. Acceptance and changes**

By using this website, you signify your consent to this privacy notice. If you do not agree to this privacy notice, please do not use our website.  If we make a material change to our privacy notice we will post the change on our website so that you may be aware of the Personal Data we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the website will signify that you agree to any such change. 

### **17\. Data Protection Contact**

Our data protection contact is Christopher Angel. For queries or comments relating to the processing of personal data please send an email to: the [dataprotection@autovistagroup.com.](mailto:dataprotection@autovistagroup.com)

If you are unhappy about the response received from the data protection contact you have the right to make a complaint to your regional Supervisory Authority.

### **18\. How to** **Contact us**  

We welcome your views about our website and our privacy notice. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments, please send an email to the dataprotection@autovistagroup.com or contact us at:

Autovista Group Limited Ltd, 5th Floor, Wellington House, 125 Strand, London WC2R 0AP.

### **19\. Date of last update**

This privacy notice was last updated in October 2018
